to you. Good day.
>> Much love
>> and to you as well.
>> A couple of questions for you. One is
based in religion and the other in
science and medicine and innovation.
>> So
>> with regards to religion, some of the
major leaders, could you expand or
expound a little bit on Moses?
>> What does Moses have to do with
religion?
I guess I'm asking you that he was a
major leader that was yes a figure
within the Old Testament.
>> We understand who you're referring to,
>> but the way we ask that question should
be very revealing to you because Moses
doesn't have to have anything at all to
do with religion to be a great teacher.
>> Yes.
>> Correct.
>> And this is true of most of what you
would call or recognize as masters. Most
of them had no intention of creating a
religion.
You understand?
>> Yes.
>> It was about helping others recognize
that they are as powerful as the teacher
teaching that everyone is or at least
has the capacity and potential to be the
same to have the same understandings and
perspectives to elevate themselves. Yes.
>> Yes. that all can be masters, all can be
teachers.
>> Yes.
>> Therefore, the misinterpretation of this
and the idea that there needs to be
somebody in between you and your
connection to creation in order to
interpret that connection for you is
what religion is.
But with your own connection and knowing
that you are self-empowered that you are
in every way equal to the idea at least
potentially of any of the ascended
masters
then you don't necessarily need to
express that through the concept of
religion unless that's simply a
permission slip that works for you.
>> Got it.
>> Does that help?
>> Yes. And I've heard about permission
slips a lot. It's very
>> by the way.
>> Yes.
Mhm.
>> If it hadn't been for the fact that an
extraterrestrial society referred to as
the Anunnaki
hadn't used their genetic material
to create the idea of Homo sapien from
the natural homminid that evolved on
your planet and created Homo sapien at
that time to be someone who should look
up to them as superior. If that hadn't
happened, it is unlikely you would ever
have developed religion on your planet.
>> That was my next question.
>> Well, I've already answered it.
>> All right. So, in relation to the
potential of the future. Yes.
>> And I know probabilities and potentials
are always a part of the future. Yes, I
do.
>> Um, and I come from a place of
innovation in healthcare and I'm just
interested in some possibilities within
neuroscience, neurology, cancer,
genetics. Yes. within the next 50 to 60
years in terms of innovation.
>> Well, you are finding out more and more
that it's all about vibration. It's all
about resonance. It's all about states
of being. that if you can find the
vibrational equation that represents a
certain state of being and you can
impose that vibrational frequency on
something that is out of alignment with
that state of being in a specific way,
you can bring it back into alignment
with that state of being which will
cause a transformation to take place
within that thing.
>> Yes.
>> That's the basis
>> interesting
>> for all you're talking about. That's the
fundamental principle behind everything
that you just asked about.
>> So on a really pragmatic level, if
somebody's really sick with heart
failure or heart disease, how do they
get back into alignment?
>> Again, they can
depending upon the reason for the
creation of that experience because not
everyone will necessarily need or want
to be healed.
>> You follow me? because they may be
creating that experience for a very
specific reason that they need to go
through or that someone else close to
them needs to experience. So you have to
look at it first on a case- by case
person by person basis as to why that's
happening.
But if there is within their choices the
probability of allowing them to heal
themselves,
then the idea can be that you need to
chart and measure what the natural
healed vibration of that particular
being would be or that particular organ
would be. And then imposing that
vibration in a specific way at a
specific frequency into that area can
either allow the tissue to regenerate
back to that vibrational state that
represents the healed state or at the
very least may cause certain
inspirations within you. If you need to
go through a process to create the
process that is necessary to bring that
organ back to a healed state by just
simply immersing in that vibration that
represents the healed state of that
organ.
>> Very cool. Thank you. Very interesting.
>> Does that help you?
>> That helps a lot. Yeah. Um
>> there is also a technique that was used
in Atlantean times that is kind of akin
to the concept of hypnosis because
in hypnosis you can actually be unlocked
from a particular reality idea and you
can be induced into another reality
idea.
More exploration on the concept of what
you now presently refer to as multiple
personality disorder
>> may be important here because there
already have been measurements of
different personalities having
completely different physical states.
Yes, one personality can actually have a
disease but when it shifts to the other
personality there's no sign of the
disease. Yes, there are case studies.
>> When you can really understand what's
going on there, you'll have your answer.
>> Yes.
>> Mhm.
>> Because they are actually, regardless of
whether it looks like it's the same
body, the same person, they are actually
two different people.
>> Yes.
>> Okay. That's
>> And there are always
>> alternate and parallel versions of
everyone. Yes. Yes.
>> Somewhere there must be a parallel
version of a person with a disease that
doesn't have it.
>> All right.
>> Finding that vibration and inducing them
to follow and match that frequency will
allow them to become that version of
themselves that not only doesn't have
the disease but never did because it's
not in their history, the new person
that they're becoming.
Yes.
Making sense? Mhm.
>> This is a way to use parallel realities
as a healing technique
and that to some degree is the future of
medicine.
>> Thanks.
>> You are welcome.
>> Appreciate it.
Hello Bashar
>> and to you. Good day.
>> I have two questions.
>> Yes.
>> Al-Qaeda.
>> Boo Haram, al-Shabaab and Islamic State.
Is there
is there a message or a commonality of
and maybe just explain kind of what's
going on? We don't we don't always get
the right uh the news stories or the
right
>> there are several things
>> things. Again, in terms of the
expression that would be the negative
side, there is, as we have already been
discussing, a lot of fear-based beliefs,
a lot of sense of being attacked, a lot
of sense of diminishment,
a lot of sense of lack of
self-empowerment.
So there is a lot of fear that reveals
itself in the lashing out that is done.
Yes.
>> Yes.
Does that answer your question
sufficiently or is there something else
you wish to understand?
>> So there's fear on on the part of the
organizations like the Islamic State or
al-Shabaab.
>> Of course they
>> again as we have already explained the
greatest power requires the gentlest
touch. If anyone has to force an idea an
ideology a perspective on anyone else
what they're saying is they don't
believe in the power of that idea.
Because if it really was a powerful
idea, why wouldn't everyone gravitate to
it? Because everyone wants to feel
powerful. Yes.
>> Yes.
>> So if an idea is not being gravitated to
yet someone believes that it should be
and forces others to do so, they don't
believe in its power either.
Yes.
>> Right. Okay. Thank you. And the second
question is in your world what kind of
leaders or do you have leaders and how
are they chosen and what is their role?
>> No no no no as we have described we
function on synchronism
pure synchronicity. Everyone is exactly
where they need to be exactly when they
need to be there just by following their
highest passion. Now there are
individuals who may choose themselves to
be organizers of sorts to help
facilitate an amplification of
synchronism in many ways to ensure that
things are running smoothly that way.
But they're not in that sense leaders.
We have no government in the way that
you choose to express that idea because
everything functions synchronistically.
We understand the mechanism of
synchronism and we use it and therefore
the leader if you want to call it that
is synchronism itself is the structure
of existence itself that we simply take
advantage of.
>> Yes.
>> Does that make sense to you?
>> Yes, it does.
>> Does that answer your question?
>> Yes.
>> Was there something else?
>> Well, I wanted to ask a little bit about
the pyramids.
>> Which ones? the Since there are so many
pyramids in in Egypt and in Asia, is
there is there also an error of when
those were built and for a certain like
global meaning when they were built?
>> The oldest ones, yes, approximately
10,500
BC as you call it. And they had great
understanding of what they were doing.
Then the knowledge was lost over time.
And a lot of the later pyramids do not
function in the same way that the
earlier ones did. The Great Pyramid of
Giza served many different kinds of
functions when it was operational in its
pristine state. Not the least of which
was that initiate priests when brought
into the understandings of the mysteries
of creation would be led into the king's
chamber and would lie down in the stone
coffer and they would be taught to
generate the gamma state in a meditation
and the stone coffer and the king's
chamber was designed to amplify and
magnify that gamma state to the point
where it reverberated and amplified and
amplified and then suddenly pop them out
of their bodies so that in astral form
they could go to higher realms, gain
knowledge, bring it back and share that
knowledge with society. Although of
course the priesthood usually kept those
things to themselves as to how they
achieved that knowledge. They would just
simply dole it out as they needed to.
You follow?
>> Mhm.
>> Does that answer your question? So could
could we do the same thing if we went
into the pyramid and
>> well yes to some degree although again
there has been some deterioration over
time so it's not really functioning at
peak performance
>> but yes it could be used as a permission
slip if you yourself
add to it
all the things that are missing in your
own energy field.
Does that make sense?
>> Yes. use your own energy field to add
the things that are now missing and you
could achieve the same effect. Yes. As a
permission slip. Of course, you don't
need the pyramid to do that necessarily.
>> Mhm.
>> But you can take advantage of that if
you wish. It's up to you.
>> Okay. Good.
>> Yes.
>> Thank you.
Hey Bashar.
>> Andy you. Good day.
>> So last session I had talked to you
about a dream that I had about
the reptilian human sexual contact.
>> Yes.
>> So um elaborating more on that um was
that a actual experience that I was
having or Yes.
it um because I also got a connection
with my subconscious mind that it also
um was connecting me more deeply with my
subconscious mind. Bringing bringing
consciousness into the subconscious.
>> Well, bringing the subconscious into the
conscious.
>> Oh yes. Bringing the subconscious into
the conscious.
>> Yes.
>> Okay. Although you are also correct in
the other direction because many of you
think that the subconscious and
unconscious are lower than your physical
conscious mind but they're not. They're
higher.
The physical mind is the lowest level.
The conscious mind is the lowest level.
>> Subconscious is above that. Unconscious
is above that because you're going
toward the idea of the higher mind.
>> Yes.
>> Yes. So, I also got the connection of
the reptilians and the Anunnaki. Um, and
I was wondering if I got a inspiration
that there's an alternate timeline where
humans were created not to mine gold.
>> Yes, of course.
>> Yes.
>> Anything you can imagine in general is
somewhere a reality. You can't imagine
non-existence,
>> right? So we there's an alternate
timeline where we were not created to
look up to them that we were created in
as equals
>> and that to some degree is where you're
shifting to.
>> Yes. That is so exciting.
>> Yes, it is.
>> Um also um
along the lines of the subconscious mind
um was the Sphinx Anabis at one time?
>> Anubis. Anubis.
>> Yes.
>> It was the jackal.
>> The jackal.
>> Not a lion. It was the jackal.
>> The god of the underworld,
>> right?
>> So to speak.
>> That's That's really awesome. Yay.
>> Does that help?
>> Yes. Uh, one more thing.
>> Yes.
>> Um, or actually two more. Does
Anubis and your Anubis
>> Anubis does Anubis and your father do
they have similar energies?
>> They do.
Thank you for picking up on that.
>> Yeah,
I I I I actually thought maybe it was
your dad, but I just they resonated so
strongly.
>> Yes, there is an energetic connection.
It's not that Anubis is my father,
>> right? But my father does have a very
strong connection to the archetypal
level consciousness that you know in
your reality as Anubis. Yes.
>> Um yeah, with all the hybridization
going on,
I mean we it's just we have so much
inside of us that doesn't usually look
that doesn't represent our physicality.
>> Yes. Um, so that's
>> there's a lot more going on in your
world than you are aware of,
>> right? And then one more thing. Uh,
thank you. Um, my alternate incarnation
in Assasani,
>> one of them.
>> Thank you. Um,
is it at the same time that you're
there?
>> Partially. There's an overlap.
>> Hello. Yay.
That's
>> all right. Hello.
>> I mean, hello in my alternate
incarnation and hello right now as of
>> um also I want to say hello to Cybo and
tell him thank you because um as you
have he also has had a very positive
impact in my life and I want to thank
him for that and you.
>> All right. Well, thank you for creating
the positive impact in your own life.
>> Yeah. Well,
>> thank you.
>> Thank you so much.
>> You are welcome so much.
>> Hello, Bashar.
>> And are you good day?
>> Happy birthday yesterday.
>> All right. Thank you.
>> What did you do?
>> Anything I wanted.
Can
>> which I do every day anyway.
>> Okay. Can we hang out for celebrate on
your birthday?
>> Can you what?
>> Hung out. Party.
>> You can have whatever party you wish.
>> Okay.
Thank you.
>> I'm not stopping you.
>> Okay. With with you.
>> Well, not with me physically.
>> Okay.
Right. Um,
>> but if you want to create a party, go
right ahead.
>> Okay. Thank you.
>> And I have a question about my sleeping
habit.
>> Your sleeping habits
>> as opposed to your natural cycle.
>> My natural cycle is
too opposite from the social.
So very opposite. Like
>> so what?
Why aren't you following your natural
sleep cycle?
>> Okay. Natural sleep cycle is most times
two two to 5:00 a.m. 6:00 a.m. I'm very
waking up.
>> Yes. Well, if you follow your excitement
and express the things that are
representative of your excitement,
>> they will most likely fall into your
natural sleep cycle instead of forcing
yourself to do things that are not
necessarily representative of your
excitement that force you to have an
unnatural sleep cycle.
>> Okay?
>> Do you understand? It's up to you,
>> right? But it's
>> more harmonious to follow your natural
cycle
>> and do the things in your life that
would then fall into place in your
natural cycle.
>> Like it's
like it's not
it's not really bother like used to be.
But still sometimes when I think about
oh I couldn't make this I couldn't make
this because I don't like waking up in
the morning. I don't I don't know. Like
>> you're just creating excuses.
>> Are you acting on your highest
excitement every moment that you
possibly can? Yes or no?
>> Yes.
>> You are. Are you sure?
>> Doesn't sound like it because you just
said you were not following your natural
sleep cycle. Wouldn't that be more
exciting
>> to be able to follow your natural cycle?
>> Yes. Yes. Yes. Then when I ask you if
you're following your excitement and you
said yes, you were fibbing.
>> Okay?
>> So stop fibbing
>> and follow your excitement. Part of
which is your natural sleep cycle. And
when you do that,
>> things may come to you in that cycle
that will be representative of things
you can do that will fall into that
natural cycle. You don't have to force
yourself to do things and have a sleep
cycle that is not natural for you
because that will make you tired,
>> right?
>> It will exhaust you.
>> It will not really refresh you.
>> You may be able to endure it for a
while,
but it won't really energize you.
Following your natural cycle will
energize you and will bring you
synchronistically the things that you
can do that will fit the cycle.
Remember, you can't experience what
you're not the vibration of first. So,
you have to be natural first in order
for synchronicity to present to you
opportunities that would fit within the
natural cycle. Otherwise, you can't see
them. that will be invisible to you
those opportunities.
>> Do you understand?
>> Yes. Very like totally. Thank you. And
>> yes.
>> And you told us fair tax because it's
close from Oakland. How about in Japan
and Las Vegas?
>> Well, that's up to the people in the
area. Now, your Las Vegas is still part
of your United States, which is
exploring the idea of the fair tax.
Japan obviously is a different culture,
>> but you can create something similar if
you wish.
>> It's up to you. We're simply saying that
that at the moment
>> is the most aligned representation for
what it is based on the economic
structure you have for what it is that
would best avail the health of the
economic structure. We're not saying
that this is the ideal scenario.
Ultimately, you will go through many
different transitions with regard to the
economics of your world and you'll have
many different ways of expressing that
idea. The idea simply right now is that
as you have designed your economic
structure, the fair tax is the one that
is most aligned for the growth and
natural health of that economic
structure at this moment.
>> Okay.
>> Does that help?
>> Yes.
>> Thank you.
>> Thank you. I have one more question.
>> I beg your pardon. I have one more
question.
>> Yes.
>> I had a dream two two weeks ago about
um Mount Chasta.
>> Yes.
>> And I will I was still remember how he
looks like
white skin, brown hair, and a little
ugly face.
And like right after I woke up, I
realized he was he was like gatekeeper
for Mount Chester.
>> In some senses, yes. Although that's a
slight interpretation in human terms,
but nevertheless. Is that some place
you're attracted to go and explore?
>> Yes.
>> When will you go?
>> Um, this Sunday night.
>> Oh, all right. Have a good time.
>> Okay.
>> And pleasant dreams.
>> Thank you.
Hi Bashar
>> and you good day.
>> I have a question to you about um doing
and being and over the last five years
I've been trying to make a transition
from my career that I've created for
myself. Um I went into nursing school.
>> Yes. and found out that the current
situation of nursing is not with what
I'm aligned with.
>> All right. What are you aligned with?
>> Well, that's what I've been pursuing in
>> pursuing
>> in my education. I wanted to take
advantage of my RN by teaching people
how to
uh take care of their bodies through
nutrition and lifestyle choices.
>> And that's exciting for you.
>> It's exceptionally exciting for me.
>> All right. So, that's what you're doing.
Yes.
>> Yes. My question though has to do with
doing and being.
>> What's the difference?
>> Because I am
>> What's the difference in your
definition?
>> Doing is like you got to do do. got this
this list of tasks that I have to
complete in order to um accomplish what
it is I'm wanting to
>> end being
>> is feels more in alignment with what you
were talking about in terms of
>> if you are in the state of being
that is appropriate for you harmonious
and in alignment with your true
frequency.
The things that you need to do
will also align with your state of being
and will not need or require effort so
much as you will simply take the natural
actions that are the natural flowing
result of being in that state. So it
won't necessarily have to be a list of
tasks that you have to do d do.
There may be some of them but remember
that synchronicity is the organizing
principle. Yes.
>> Yes.
>> And if it is the organizing principle
which it is then by acting on your
excitement
the things that come with the highest
excitement in whatever order that they
come are the things that need doing. But
you will do them from a state of being
that allows them to also be exciting
actions.
And it will not be more than you need to
do. It will regulate itself in order, in
timing, in everything in such a way as
to show you exactly what needs to be
done and when. And no more than that
will be needed.
Does this help?
Are you understanding this concept?
>> It does. I
>> Yeah,
>> in translating it in my life has been
the challenge because I've been
applying what you talk about, I'd say.
>> But you're not. That's the point. You're
not not quite.
You're still allowing outdated
definitions to create a sense
within you that more needs to be done
than may need to be done. You're not
letting synchronicity show you what
needs to be done. You're making an
assumption of what you need to do.
>> Yes.
>> I guess so.
>> You guess or you know. So
>> it's just I feel like I'm doing okay. So
I don't I'm not getting paid.
>> Let's take it to a specific level
>> to help illustrate the point.
>> Can you describe the idea now? You're
doing what excites you. Yes.
>> Can you describe the idea of this list
of tasks and how you create that?
>> Okay. I'm working with Okay. I have
three people that I work with.
>> Yes.
>> And that when I work with them, it
really elicits that feeling of
excitement. I love it. They're making
changes. We all are really excited
>> and so
>> okay so where does the
>> there's this on this side over here and
then there's what I've been doing for
work over here and I'm trying to make
the leap of see these people aren't
paying me. I'm doing it to elicit that
feeling of excitement but I haven't
>> like to get out and to market what I'm
doing requires time. So there's more
things that I have to do.
>> So what why isn't that part of your
excitement?
because it's one more thing that I have
to do with all the
>> one more thing. If you were doing it in
the way that is exciting for you, it
would be one more thing you wouldn't be
able to wait to do. You're not doing it
in alignment with excitement. That's
what we're saying. You're making those
things look like tasks, defining them as
something other than your excitement. If
those things actually need to be done,
there is a way to do them that is part
and parcel of your excitement and you're
not doing them that way. That's why they
feel like they don't belong. That's why
they feel like tasks because you're
using old definitions about the way
you're going about doing those things or
think that you have to go about doing
those things and making them non-exiting
>> when you could be inventing ways to do
the things that need to be done in more
exciting ways by using your imagination
and not just assuming there's only one
way to do these things to get the word
out to market yourself.
You're limiting your imagination with
these definitions that limit you.
>> Yes.
>> Can we use your imagination to come up
with something as you would say in your
language out of the box to advertise and
market yourself in a way that would be
more exciting for you? Will you allow
your imagination the free reign to do
that or are you going to keep it in a
box?
>> I will take it out of the box.
>> All right. So now open up your
imagination and now comes the idea of
I'm excited to market myself to get the
word out that I'm doing this. That is
exciting. Yes, just getting the word
out. Is that exciting?
>> Relating to people is exciting to me and
then it naturally flows from me when I
do that. So yes, that is exciting.
>> So first question, why isn't that
enough?
because I'm still compressing my vision
around that I've got to work this amount
of hours per week to make enough money
and then when I get home I'm dead tired
and I'm like
>> then why don't you charge more?
>> I have been I've jumped up my rates a
lot.
>> Do you feel good or bad about doing
that?
>> I feel fine about it, but I kind of feel
like I've reached the ceiling for what
I'm doing and now I'm trying to make the
leap over to what I'm wanting to be
truly doing. But you keep going back and
forth here.
>> You keep going back and forth between
two different completely different
ideas.
>> I know. That's what I'm living is two
completely different ideas.
>> But stop.
>> That's what we're saying. Why aren't you
just living your excitement? Don't you
believe it can support you?
>> I do, but it's like no no no no.
you're already in trouble
when that question is asked.
Anything other than yes is a no. So I do
but
>> means no. Do you understand? Because if
you really knew that it would support
you, you would simply say yes, I know
that you would know it. So here's the
crux. Here's the issue. You don't know
that it can support you. You're not
sure. You don't believe it.
That's where you need to focus.
>> Okay.
>> Yes.
>> What are you afraid of? Why don't you
believe that what really excites you can
support you?
because of the complexity of
relationship and talking about money and
how is bringing that into
the dynamics of a relationship and
saying I mean
>> what are you saying
>> is this another way of saying that you
don't like to charge for your services
>> no no no
>> what are you saying
>> I'm saying that
I have to make I'm making money to
support my family and myself
>> I understand and you do understand that
the definition of abundance is wider
than just money. Yes.
>> Yes, I do.
>> Are you sure?
>> I'm Yes.
>> All right. So, why don't you believe
that what excites you can support you in
the way you need to be supported to
continue to act on your excitement?
Because that's one of the tools in the
kit, you know.
>> Yeah.
>> That it supports you to allow you to
continue to do your excitement in
whatever way you need to be supported.
Not the way you may think you need to be
supported. In the way you need to be
supported.
>> Yes.
>> Big difference.
>> So,
are you afraid that your excitement
can't support you?
>> Yes or no?
Hesitation.
>> No. No. No. It's just like this. It's
like jumping off a cliff.
>> Exactly. And I would encourage you not
to do so if you don't know that you have
a parachute.
So what you're saying is you're holding
on to old beliefs that you believe you
need, old things that you believe you
need for support. And that's fine
as long as you are at least allowing
yourself to do the things that excite
you to some degree. It can over time
demonstrate to you, prove to you that it
can support you. The question is, how
long are you willing to wait?
>> I'm Well, my goal is to start at the
beginning of the year. I kind of feel
like the end of the year.
>> But are you afraid to?
>> I'm excited and afraid. I mean, I am
excited.
>> Which is it?
>> I'm Yes.
>> They're not the same thing.
>> It's There's a They're mixed. They're
together.
>> No, you go back and forth. I've
>> You're like a little pingpong ball.
>> Exactly.
>> So you are excited sometimes, you're
afraid other times. So in the meantime,
use that process. Find the things that
you're afraid of. Find the beliefs that
generate the fear. Identify them. Let
them go. That's your task right now.
So that when you clear yourself out, you
will just be excited and you will know
it can support you.
>> Yes.
>> Yes. Does that help?
>> It helps tremendously.
>> Are you a little bit more excited now?
>> I'm a lot more excited.
>> Oh, all right. Thank you.
>> Thank you.
>> Hello, Taba.
>> Nania, is it time for Cosmic News
Network?
>> It is.
>> Okay, back to the election now.
>> Not yet.
>> What time is it?
Uh, I think we have about 10 minutes.
>> I didn't ask you that, did I?
>> I'm not going to tell you.
>> Oh, all right.
This is Cosmic News Network signing off.
>> No, no, no, no, no, no.
>> What time is it?
>> No, cuz some people ask questions and we
>> 3:30. Can we have 10 minutes?
>> Thank you for asking.
>> I did.
>> Did you?
No, you told me.
>> No, no, no, no, no.
Somebody help me here.
>> I don't want to get into trouble with
you.
>> Too late.
>> Please proceed.
>> Okay. Um, Trump appears to be a bit
dumbfounded by having his bluff called.
Is that
>> Well, it's very rare that someone is
smartfounded.
So, is there a chance that the
seriousness of this sinks in and makes
him a better person?
>> There's a chance.
>> What are the odds?
>> Even
because of that narcissistic
narcissistic
>> It's too soon to tell.
>> It's still too fresh.
Remember that you're not the only ones
in shock.
>> Yeah, he's in shock, too. Right.
With the new president, do we have a
better chance of avoiding the economic
collapse that was predicted or the major
economic
devaluation?
>> You do have better odds in certain ways.
Yes.
>> And the risk of a terrorist incident
>> still pending,
but we'll see. There are moves that need
to be made first that will tell us more.
that have to do, as you already know,
with Jerusalem.
>> Yes. In fact, Trump said that they were
talking about moving the capital of
Israel to Jerusalem.
>> Yes. And that will start something
moving.
But we'll see. There are other pathways
through it other than a terrorist
attack, but we'll see. It's too soon to
tell.
>> Um, one person wanted to know if the
shift to the parallel Earth will contain
any Republicans
in the sense that there will be an
interim period where it will be more
representative of the original republic
than yes, but not in the way that they
exist now. So as the parallel realities
get farther and farther apart, will
literally you stop seeing at some point
the people who are of opposing
viewpoints?
>> Yes, eventually.
>> But that's not like for a long time,
right?
>> Long is relative. Some people may see it
in their lifetime. Others may see it in
a generation or two.
Depends on how they're looking. Depends
on their perspective. depends on their
process. Depends on how long they may
need something of opposition to hang
around as a reflection. Depends.
This one's a really cool one. This one
says, "The first day Trump takes office
is January 21, 2017, and Trump will be
70 years old. 7 months and seven days
that day."
>> There you go.
>> What does that tell you? Lucky seven.
that it's not an accident.
>> Um, and with all these protests, what
are some of the benefits of all the
protests that are happening?
>> Well, again, certainly you can see that
there are different reality perspectives
here. Now, of course, the lashing out is
not necessarily constructive, but the
protest demonstrates in general that
there are truly different realities
here. You're beginning to recognize that
it's actually being shown to you that
there are different realities side by
side.
>> Is there any chance that the electorate
college will not support Trump?
>> Not much of a chance that it will not,
but
you may find that within about 15 to 20
of your years, there will no longer be
an electoral college. That's got a
higher probability.
>> Yeah, there definitely were some people
who wanted to know that. Um will
let's see
um what if Donald Donald Trump
implements unjust laws like
discrimination and things like that?
What is the appropriate way to respond
to things like that?
>> Compassion.
>> Does that mean that you should break the
law or should you follow that law or how
does that work?
>> We cannot advise you on that,
>> right? because we never advise you to
break a law. But we understand the idea
that sometimes what you would call a
quote unquote just rebellion may require
it. But we cannot be engaged in your
politics to that degree to advise you on
that one way or the other.
>> Okay. And then lastly, um, what
percentage of Earth's population
contributed genetically to the
hybridization program?
>> About 15%.
>> And so of the people in this room, what
percentage of these people are involved
in the hybridization program?
>> About 75%.
And um do you know what happened to
Napoleon when he was inside the great
pyramid in Egypt?
>> He had a vision.
>> Do you know what his vision was?
>> He actually had a division
of his defeat
>> and sought to see if it could be
changed.
because he stumbled into a vibration
that represented a parallel timeline. He
understood there were other options but
did not really understand the amount of
momentum that was behind the timeline he
was already established for himself.
>> That's interesting. Okay. And lastly,
for those of us who are joining us in
Europe and are quite concerned about
what's happening in Europe, that
there's, you know, there's a lot of
antagonism around the refugees coming
into their country and that it seems
like the immigration issue is a big one
here, too.
>> Yes. And so they were wondering what you
could share with us about this mirror
reflection that's happening in both
locations and what is the best way to
approach the whole situation
>> at this time. That is a subject that we
would need to spend more time on and we
will not address it at present.
>> Okay. So but in terms of the people in
Europe feel staying calm I guess with
all the change.
>> Absolutely. It's the same ideas that
we've had here.
>> Yes.
>> Which is that you find a positive way to
>> find the path through it. Now that all
bets are off, you have the opportunity
to start crystallizing a reality of your
preference in a variety of ways by
acting on your passion. Because now
everything is unlocked.
Now you don't have to rely on what's
expected. The unexpected has now reared
its head so strongly that you are truly
unlocked from the idea of any
expectation other than those that are
truly relevant. So allow yourself to
take advantage of this limbo state by
understanding there is very little now
restricting you from crystallizing the
reality that you prefer.
>> Okay. Well, thank you. Thank you for
that update from the Cosmic News
Network. It is our pleasure.
>> And
since you're in charge, what would you
like to do now?
>> We would be very excited for all of you
to take a short break and then we will
resume the transmission with your
holotope experience.
>> Okay.